<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>godteeth's news</title>
  <link>https://godteeth.com/news.html</link>
  <description>interesting news i found</description>
  <language>en-us</language>

  <item>
    <title>France set to allow police to spy through phones</title>
    <link>https://www.lemonde.fr/en/france/article/2023/07/06/france-set-to-allow-police-to-spy-through-phones_6044269_7.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 10:04:00 +0200</pubDate>
    <description>French lawmakers agreed to a justice reform bill that includes a provision granting police the power to get suspects' geolocation through phones and other devices.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Judge rules White House pressured social networks to “suppress free speech”</title>
    <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2023/07/judge-rules-white-house-pressured-social-networks-to-suppress-free-speech</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023 13:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>A federal judge yesterday ordered the Biden administration to halt a wide range of communications with social media companies, siding with Missouri and Louisiana in a lawsuit that alleges Biden and his administration violated the First Amendment by colluding with social networks "to suppress disfavored speakers, viewpoints, and content."</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Barred from grocery stores by facial recognition</title>
    <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2023/06/28/technology/facial-recognition-shoplifters-britain.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>British merchants are increasingly using the technology to combat shoplifting, raising questions about its spread as artificial intelligence rapidly improves it.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Amazon shuts down customer’s smart home devices after delivery driver’s false racism claim</title>
    <link>https://nypost.com/2023/06/15/amazon-shuts-down-customers-smart-home-devices-over-false-racist-claim/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:28:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Amazon shut off a man’s smart home devices for a week after a delivery driver falsely accused the customer of hurling a racial slur via a doorbell intercom, the tech giant confirmed Thursday.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Scientists say first synthetic human "embryo" created</title>
    <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2023/6/15/scientists-say-first-synthetic-human-embryo-created</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Research says embryo-like structures will lack organs such as a beating heart or a brain, but include cells that would typically go on to form the placenta, yolk sac and the embryo itself.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Psychedelics reopen the social reward learning critical period</title>
    <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-023-06204-3#article-info</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Here we demonstrate in mice that the ability to reopen the social reward learning critical period is a shared property across psychedelic drugs. Notably, the time course of critical period reopening is proportional to the duration of acute subjective effects reported in humans.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Facial recognition finds alleged Bosnian war criminal hiding in Tennessee, DHS claims</title>
    <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2023/06/13/facial-recognition-finds-a-bosnian-war-criminal-hiding-in-tennessee-dhs-claims/?sh=269554123188</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:08:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Bosnia and Herzegovina is still searching for war criminals from the Bosnian War. One has been living a quiet life in Tennessee, according to the DHS, which arrested him this month.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>For the sixth year, Algeria blocks internet nationwide to prevent cheating during final exams</title>
    <link>https://www.newarab.com/news/algeria-blocks-internet-stop-cheating-during-final-exams</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>This is the sixth year Algeria decides to block the internet, and their senior officials, say, unfortunately,  other solutions do not work.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>An electric cruise ship with gigantic sails is set to launch in 2030</title>
    <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/hurtigruten-norway-zero-emission-cruise-ship-climate-c2e-spc-intl</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 07:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Adventure cruise company Hurtigruten Norway today revealed plans for a zero-emissions electric cruise ship with retractable sails covered in solar panels, which is due to set sail in 2030</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>FBI PSA: Malicious actors manipulating photos and videos to create explicit content and sextortion schemes</title>
    <link>https://www.ic3.gov/Media/Y2023/PSA230605</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>The FBI is warning the public of malicious actors creating synthetic content (commonly referred to as "deepfakes") by manipulating benign photographs or videos to target victims.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Paralyzed man walks naturally, thanks to wireless ‘bridge’ between brain and spine</title>
    <link>https://www.science.org/content/article/paralyzed-man-walks-naturally-thanks-wireless-bridge-brain-spine</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Implanted brain electrodes send signals that bypass damaged spinal cord area, using man’s thoughts to stimulate leg movement</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>India first democracy to ban encrypted messaging apps on massive scale</title>
    <link>https://tutanota.com/blog/posts/apps-banned-india</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Only days before Press Freedom Day, India banned apps for secure communication because of "terrorists" use.</description>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>
