<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>godteeth's news</title>
  <link>https://godteeth.com/news.html</link>
  <description>interesting news i found</description>
  <language>en-us</language>

  <item>
    <title>Amazon shuts down customer’s smart home devices after delivery driver’s false racism claim</title>
    <link>https://nypost.com/2023/06/15/amazon-shuts-down-customers-smart-home-devices-over-false-racist-claim/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:28:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Amazon shut off a man’s smart home devices for a week after a delivery driver falsely accused the customer of hurling a racial slur via a doorbell intercom, the tech giant confirmed Thursday.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>West Darfur governor abducted, killed as war in Sudan spreads</title>
    <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2023/6/15/west-darfur-governor-abducted-killed-as-war-in-sudan-spreads</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>West Darfur state governor Khamis Abakar killed after TV interview accusing paramilitary fighters of killing civilians in large numbers and calling for international intervention.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Scientists say first synthetic human "embryo" created</title>
    <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2023/6/15/scientists-say-first-synthetic-human-embryo-created</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Research says embryo-like structures will lack organs such as a beating heart or a brain, but include cells that would typically go on to form the placenta, yolk sac and the embryo itself.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>An electric cruise ship with gigantic sails is set to launch in 2030</title>
    <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/hurtigruten-norway-zero-emission-cruise-ship-climate-c2e-spc-intl</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 07:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Adventure cruise company Hurtigruten Norway today revealed plans for a zero-emissions electric cruise ship with retractable sails covered in solar panels, which is due to set sail in 2030</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>FBI PSA: Malicious actors manipulating photos and videos to create explicit content and sextortion schemes</title>
    <link>https://www.ic3.gov/Media/Y2023/PSA230605</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>The FBI is warning the public of malicious actors creating synthetic content (commonly referred to as "deepfakes") by manipulating benign photographs or videos to target victims.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Paralyzed man walks naturally, thanks to wireless ‘bridge’ between brain and spine</title>
    <link>https://www.science.org/content/article/paralyzed-man-walks-naturally-thanks-wireless-bridge-brain-spine</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <description>Implanted brain electrodes send signals that bypass damaged spinal cord area, using man’s thoughts to stimulate leg movement</description>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>
